Hello friends, I am Sagar and a
very warm welcome to all of you in this video of ours.
In today's video, we are going to talk
about the stock of Ad Long Bar General Insurance. How is this
quarter good? The result during the market closing.
Now its direct view will be seen by the Inter College
staff. Yesterday,
you saw the results of Case Life today. There was a
big fall of 565 in the stock. So are the
results encouraging here?
Here too, the same kind of beating will be seen. We will
try to find out.
First of all, let's take a look at
whatever number is seen here, friends. And
in the last, I will convert it into crores and
talk about
quit standalone number here. If you are
looking at it here, for the December quarter, first of all
we will talk about cross
premium return. Here, the
premium coming out of this cotton is seen to be
around 4,776. In the last quarter, the
figure was around 7500.28 crores. So
from there, you will see the PM increasing this time
and last year this number was
but of 4111 crores. So from there  I am telling you that there is a
significant increase here
and if we talk about the
profit numbers of this company after taking out all the things, then friends, the profit numbers that
you are seeing here,
friends, will
not be that much fun, the profit after tax
number that is seen coming is
317 crores in this quarter, the
company has posted 313 crores for last year,
so just chart the
profit that evening, it was seen increasing on a 10 year basis,
but if you look at it
from the previous quarter, you will
see a glass here, from
440 crores the profit which the company
posted, then somewhere there is a negative of 130 crores,
you get to see cricket here,
not that there is a
decline here, there is a 1.25 percent increase in the previous profit, so here it is
not considered that big a number, it is not that
great, as much as it will not be considered subscribed here
to see the subscribe numbers,
subscribe,
subscribe, this is what you are seeing  If the
subscription was 90 then somewhere here
disappointment was seen in the subscribe
form of the house, you saw a big fall here,
1675 whose hand was there, it was a
little above around 1295, click for a week,
all the channels started that are present here,
but if you try to think about it in the chart,
subscribe and subscribe somewhere here,
if you have any question here, then whoever
subscribes here, then
subscribe,
this entry, the collection that has come here,
go to another game, you can see, if there is a
big fall here, then you
can see it coming around the level, now the
school staff should close this level again,
here the double top gasser formation is
looking completely different from the previous one,
click the subscribe button here, subscribe,
but friends, in this way,
you have to subscribe,
friends, subscribe to the channel by making a lot of money here,
subscribe here, the
subscribe at the bottom has definitely been
subscribing, there has
not been a big range, so the best way to play it in this range is that
if it
comes at the bottom of this transparent dress, then
with a stop loss there  Brother,
try to do it and if it tries to go towards one side,
then you can
try to share there with pit stop loss, there is
no opinion of trading portion in this, due to deadlock you can
see white springs on both sides,
so friends I hope you
liked the video, if you liked the video then
like and share it
with your friends, if you have not subscribed to the channel then do
subscribe to the channel, Rajput
in his next video, till then goodbye,
thank you to